A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, West Africa Program, RG 5 FA1766
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, West Africa Program, RG 5
1953-1977 (Bulk: 1957-1963)
1957-1963
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Brothers Fund
FA1766
12.4 Cubic Feet
Biographical / Historical
The West Africa Program of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund, launched late in 1957, was designed to provide technical assistance tailored to the economic development needs of Ghana and Nigeria. While the Fund's original resolve to aid Liberia in the same manner proved unfruitful, the Republic of Togo also became a beneficiary of this program in a minor way.
Under the limits established by the Fund, the West Africa Program did not operate as a grant-making agency. At the request of ministries in one of the African governments involved or of a private group of investors and industrialists, the Fund contracted with outside consultants to prepare "feasibility studies." Each of these studies dealt in depth with a specific aspect of the concerned nation's economic potential or needs and was designed to provide a realistic framework for later action. The Fund's responsibility ended with the submission of these studies to the appropriate agencies or private groups.
The Program's main office in Lagos, Nigeria was also a distribution point for these studies. Its director, Robert I. Fleming, acted as a liaison between the governments of Togo, Ghana, and Nigeria and groups of U.S. investors. The Lagos office organized investigative tours for these investors and arranged their contacts with governmental personnel.
The West Africa Program of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund was concluded at the end of 1962.
Scope and Contents
The records of the West Africa Program include correspondence from the New York and Lagos offices, memoranda, reports, administrative and financial materials, personnel correspondence, and a complete set of feasibility studies contracted by the Rockefeller Brothers Fund. The bulk of this material dates between 1957 and 1963, the period during which the Lagos office was in full operation.
Arrangement
The records of the West Africa Program are divided into three series:
Series 1 - General Files
Series 2 - Projects
Series 3 - Feasibility Studies
Series 1044 - Photographs
Note: These records were reviewed and partially weeded by Rockefeller Brothers Fund officials in 1968. At that time the original filing order of the documents was not retained.
Conditions Governing Access
All material more than ten years old is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund West Africa Program were deposited with the Rockefeller Archive Center on January 10, 1979 and later donated to RAC.
- West Africa Program, 1953-1977, bulk 1957-1963; 1957-1963; 5; 12.4 Cubic Feet 30 boxes
  Biographical/Historical note
  The West Africa Program of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund, launched late in 1957, was designed to provide technical assistance tailored to the economic development needs of Ghana and Nigeria. While the Fund's original resolve to aid Liberia in the same manner proved unfruitful, the Republic of Togo also became a beneficiary of this program in a minor way.
  Under the limits established by the Fund, the West Africa Program did not operate as a grant-making agency. At the request of ministries in one of the African governments involved or of a private group of investors and industrialists, the Fund contracted with outside consultants to prepare "feasibility studies." Each of these studies dealt in depth with a specific aspect of the concerned nation's economic potential or needs and was designed to provide a realistic framework for later action. The Fund's responsibility ended with the submission of these studies to the appropriate agencies or private groups.
  The Program's main office in Lagos, Nigeria was also a distribution point for these studies. Its director, Robert I. Fleming, acted as a liaison between the governments of Togo, Ghana, and Nigeria and groups of U.S. investors. The Lagos office organized investigative tours for these investors and arranged their contacts with governmental personnel.
  The West Africa Program of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund was concluded at the end of 1962.
  Scope and Contents note
  The records of the West Africa Program include correspondence from the New York and Lagos offices, memoranda, reports, administrative and financial materials, personnel correspondence, and a complete set of feasibility studies contracted by the Rockefeller Brothers Fund. The bulk of this material dates between 1957 and 1963, the period during which the Lagos office was in full operation.
  Arrangement note
  The records of the West Africa Program are divided into three series:
  Series 1 - General Files
  Series 2 - Projects
  Series 3 - Feasibility Studies
  Series 1044 - Photographs
  Note: These records were reviewed and partially weeded by Rockefeller Brothers Fund officials in 1968. At that time the original filing order of the documents was not retained.
  Conditions Governing Access
  All material more than ten years old is open for research.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition note
  The records of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund West Africa Program were deposited with the Rockefeller Archive Center on January 10, 1979.
  - General Files, 1957-1977, bulk 1957-1963; 1957-1963; 1; 4 Cubic Feet
    This series contains correspondence, memoranda, reports, financial and administrative material, personnel correspondence and news releases.
    - Action Affecting the Climate for Investment, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Action Affecting the Climate for Investment, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Agency for International Development (AID) / Arthur D. Little, Incorporated, 1961-1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Articles Published, 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Budgets and Accounting, 1958-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Budgets and Accounting, 1958-1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Camp, John R. - Survey Trip Correspondence, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Camp, John R. - Survey Trip Correspondence, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Camp, John R. - Survey Trip Report, 1957 June (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Capital Plant - Equipment and Furnishings for Office and Flat, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Checci and Company - Contract, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Checci Study - Correspondence, 1960 March - 1963 June (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Checci Study - Correspondence, 1960 March - 1963 June (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Checci Study - Correspondence, 1960 March - 1963 June (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Checci Study - Memoranda, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Checci Study - Report, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Confidential File - Incoming Letters from New York, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Confidential File - Incoming Letters from New York, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Confidential File - Incoming Letters from New York, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Confidential File - Incoming Letters from New York, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Confidential File - Incoming Letters from New York, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Confidential File - Incoming Letters from New York, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Confidential File - Incoming Letters from New York, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Confidential File - Outgoing Letters to New York, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Confidential File - Outgoing Letters to New York, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Confidential File - Outgoing Letters to New York, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Confidential File - Outgoing Letters to New York, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Confidential File - Outgoing Letters to New York, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence (General), 1958-1963 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence (General), 1958-1963 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Feasibility Studies - Agency for International Development (AID) Index, 1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Feasibility Studies - Correspondence with Arthur D. Little, Incorporated, 1962-1967 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Feasibility Studies - Requests to New York Office, 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Feasibility Studies - Requests to New York Office, 1966-1977 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Fleming, Robert I. - Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Fleming, Robert I. - Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Fleming, Robert I. - Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Fleming, Robert I. - Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Fleming, Robert I. - Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Hyde, James N. - Trips, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 0039A)
    - Ivory Coast - Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Incidental Expenses Associated with Program, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Insurance - Automobile, 1958-1963 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Insurance - Personnel - Accident, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Legal Documents, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Library, 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - May, Stacy - Correspondence with Robert I. Fleming, 1958-1962 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - May, Stacy - Correspondence with Robert I. Fleming, 1958-1962 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - May, Stacy - Correspondence with Robert I. Fleming, 1958-1962 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - May, Stacy - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - May, Stacy - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - May, Stacy - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - May, Stacy - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - News Releases, 1958-1962 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - News Releases, 1958-1962 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - New York Files, 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - New York Files, 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - New York Files, 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - New York Files, 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - New York Files, 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - New York Files, 1962-1968 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - New York Files, 1962-1968 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - New York Files, 1962-1968 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - New York Files, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Office and Flat - Rent, 1958-1965 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Personnel - Miscellany, 1958-1963 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Personnel - Claire Ackauku, 1959-1964 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Personnel - Nicholas G. Carter, 1960-1962 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Personnel - James Larkin, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Public Relations and Entertainment, 1959-1963 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Stonehill, Harry S., 1960-1968 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Togo - Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Finance - Correspondence Relating to Finance in General, 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Finance - Correspondence Relating to Finance in General, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Finance - Cashbook, 1959-1963 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Finance - Voucher Books 2-3, 1960 February 1-March 30 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Finance - Voucher Book 4, 1960 April (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Final Audits, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 226)
    - Voucher Book 2, 1959 October - 1960 February (Box 29, Folder 227)
    - Analytical Cash Book for Lagos Office, 1960 January - 1963 January (Box 30, Folder 230)
  - Projects, 1953-1965, bulk 1958-1965; 1958-1965; 2; 6 Cubic Feet
    This series contains correspondence, memoranda, and reports related to projects undertaken in Togo, Ghana, and Nigeria.
    - Togo - Development Bank - Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Togo - Development Bank - Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Togo - Development Bank - Reports, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - Togo - Economic Information, 1958-1960 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Ghana - Electrical Assembly Plant, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Ghana - Fisheries, 1953, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Ghana - Paradigm Site Material, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - Ghana - Poultry, 1958-1961 (Box 11, Folder 87)
    - Ghana - Poultry, 1958-1961 (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - Ghana - Water Project, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - Ghana - Water Project, 1959 February - 1961 May (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - Ghana - Water Project, 1959 February - 1961 May (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - Ghana - Water Project, 1959 February - 1961 May (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - Ghana - Water Project, 1959 February - 1961 May (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Ghana - Water Project, 1959 February - 1961 May (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - Nigeria - Bicycle Tire Manufacturing, 1959-1961 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Nigeria - Boats (Wooden), 1961 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Nigeria - Bornu Province, 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Nigeria - Building Costs, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - Nigeria - Cable and Wire, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - Nigeria - Candle Manufacturing, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Nigeria - Cement, 1960-1962 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Nigeria - Cement, 1960-1962 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - Nigeria - Ceramics (Clay-Tile), 1959-1963 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Nigeria - Ceramics (Clay-Tile), 1959-1963 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Nigeria - Chalk Project, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - Nigeria - Cigar Industry, 1960 June - 1963 March (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - Nigeria - Cigar Industry, 1960 June - 1963 March (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - Nigeria - Cigarette Project, 1960-1962 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - Nigeria - Cinema Development, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - Nigeria - Cinva Ram Project, 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 110)
    - Nigeria - Cinva Ram Project, 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 111)
    - Nigeria - Cinva Ram Project - International Volunteer Services, 1959-1961 (Box 14, Folder 112)
    - Nigeria - Coal Products, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    - Nigeria - Coastal Shipping, undated (Box 14, Folder 114)
    - Nigeria - Coffee, 1960-1963 (Box 14, Folder 115)
    - Nigeria - Concrete Products, 1960-1963 (Box 14, Folder 116)
    - Nigeria - Cooperage, 1959-1960, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 117)
    - Nigeria - Core Stock Veneer, 1962-1965 (Box 15, Folder 118)
    - Nigeria - Cotton Textiles, 1958-1961 (Box 15, Folder 119)
    - Nigeria - Cylinders and Stove Project, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 120)
    - Nigeria - Deep Sea Fishing, 1959-1962 (Box 15, Folder 121)
    - Nigeria - Dry Cleaning Project, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 122)
    - Nigeria - Electrical Assembly Project, 1959-1962 (Box 15, Folder 123)
    - Nigeria - Electrical Assembly Project, 1959-1962 (Box 15, Folder 124)
    - Nigeria - Fertilizer, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 125)
    - Nigeria - Fish, 1959, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 126)
    - Nigeria - Flour Mill Project, 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 127)
    - Nigeria - Food Processing Project, 1959-1962 (Box 16, Folder 128)
    - Nigeria - Furniture Project, 1957-1961 (Box 16, Folder 129)
    - Nigeria - Glass Project, 1959 May - 1961 February (Box 16, Folder 130)
    - Nigeria - Glass Project, 1959 May - 1961 February (Box 16, Folder 131)
    - Nigeria - Glass Project, 1959 May - 1961 February (Box 16, Folder 132)
    - Nigeria - Glass Project, 1959 May - 1961 February (Box 16, Folder 133)
    - Nigeria - Glass Project, 1959 May - 1961 February (Box 16, Folder 134)
    - Nigeria - Glass Project, 1959 May - 1961 February (Box 16, Folder 135)
    - Nigeria - Glass Project, 1961-1963 (Box 17, Folder 136)
    - Nigeria - Glass Project, 1961-1963 (Box 17, Folder 137)
    - Nigeria - Glass Project, 1961-1963 (Box 17, Folder 138)
    - Nigeria - Glue and Resin Project, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 139)
    - Nigeria - Gramophone Records, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 140)
    - Nigeria - Gravel Crushing Project, 1960-1963 (Box 17, Folder 141)
    - Nigeria - Gypsum Deposit, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 142)
    - Nigeria - Hotels, 1959-1963 (Box 17, Folder 143)
    - Nigeria - Housing - Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 17, Folder 144)
    - Nigeria - Housing - Reports, 1959-1962 (Box 17, Folder 145)
    - Nigeria - Industrial Estate Project, 1960, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 146)
    - Nigeria - Investment Fund, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 147)
    - Nigeria - Iron and Steel, 1960 January - 1963 May (Box 18, Folder 148)
    - Nigeria - Iron and Steel, 1960 January - 1963 May (Box 18, Folder 149)
    - Nigeria - Iron and Steel, 1960 January - 1963 May (Box 18, Folder 150)
    - Nigeria - Iron and Steel, 1960 January - 1963 May (Box 18, Folder 151)
    - Nigeria - Iron and Steel, 1960 January - 1963 May (Box 18, Folder 152)
    - Nigeria - Kenof Fiber Bag Project, 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 153)
    - Nigeria - Kenof Fiber Bag Project, 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 154)
    - Nigeria - Kerosene Project, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 155)
    - Nigeria - Lead Pencil Project, 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 156)
    - Nigeria - Lead Products, 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 157)
    - Nigeria - Leather Tanneries, 1959-1963 (Box 19, Folder 158)
    - Nigeria - Lumber, 1958-1960 August (Box 19, Folder 159)
    - Nigeria - Lumber, 1958-1960 August (Box 19, Folder 160)
    - Nigeria - Lumber, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 161)
    - Nigeria - Lumber, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 162)
    - Nigeria - Lumber - Reports, 1959-1963 (Box 20, Folder 163)
    - Nigeria - Machete Project, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 164)
    - Nigeria - Management Training Project, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 165)
    - Nigeria - Matches, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 166)
    - Nigeria - Meat Packing Project, 1959-1963 (Box 20, Folder 167)
    - Nigeria - Meat Packing Project, 1959-1963 (Box 20, Folder 168)
    - Nigeria - Motorized Pushcarts, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 169)
    - Nigeria - Nails, 1960-1961, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 170)
    - Nigeria - Natural Gas Transmission, 1959-1962 (Box 21, Folder 171)
    - Nigeria - Nuts and Bolts, 1961-1963 (Box 21, Folder 172)
    - Nigeria - Oil Processing, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 173)
    - Nigeria - Paints, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 174)
    - Nigeria - Paper Cup Project, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 175)
    - Nigeria - Paper Production, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 176)
    - Nigeria - Pharmaceutical Marketing, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 177)
    - Nigeria - Pharmaceuticals, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 178)
    - Nigeria - Pharmaceuticals, 1961-1964 (Box 22, Folder 179)
    - Nigeria - Pharmaceuticals, 1961-1964 (Box 22, Folder 180)
    - Nigeria - Plastics, 1959-1963 (Box 22, Folder 181)
    - Nigeria - Plastics, 1959-1963 (Box 22, Folder 182)
    - Nigeria - Plastics, 1959-1963 (Box 22, Folder 183)
    - Nigeria - Plastics - Reports, 1959-1962 (Box 22, Folder 184)
    - Nigeria - Poultry, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 185)
    - Nigeria - Printing, 1958-1960 (Box 22, Folder 186)
    - Nigeria - Publications, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 187)
    - Nigeria - Publications, 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 188)
    - Nigeria - Publications - Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 189)
    - Nigeria - Refrigerator Project, 1959-1961 (Box 23, Folder 190)
    - Nigeria - Restaurants, 1959-1960, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 191)
    - Nigeria - Rice Production, 1954, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 192)
    - Nigeria - Rubber Products, 1959-1963 (Box 23, Folder 193)
    - Nigeria - Salt, Caustic Soda, and Chlorine, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 194)
    - Nigeria - Salt, Caustic Soda, and Chlorine - Reports, 1958-1961 (Box 23, Folder 195)
    - Nigeria - Shirt Manufacturing, 1960-1961, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 196)
    - Nigeria - Starch Manufacturing, 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 197)
    - Nigeria - Textiles, 1959-1963 May (Box 24, Folder 198)
    - Nigeria - Textiles, 1959-1963 May (Box 24, Folder 199)
    - Nigeria - Textiles, 1959-1963 May (Box 24, Folder 200)
    - Nigeria - Textiles, 1959-1963 May (Box 24, Folder 201)
    - Nigeria - Textiles, 1959-1963 May (Box 24, Folder 202)
    - Nigeria - Textiles, 1959-1963 May (Box 24, Folder 203)
    - Nigeria - Textiles - Reports, 1959-1962 (Box 24, Folder 204)
    - Nigeria - Government - Western Region, 1958-1960, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 205)
    - Nigeria - Government - Eastern Region, 1959-1963 (Box 25, Folder 206)
    - Nigeria - Government - Northern Region, 1959-1963 (Box 25, Folder 207)
    - Ghana - Poultry Breeding Report, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 228)
    - Nigeria - Reports (Box 29, Folder 229)
      Bornu Province, 1956
      Glass, 1959
      Iron and Steel, 1960
      Salt, 1962
      Leather, undated
  - Feasibilities Studies, 1959-1963; 3; 2 Cubic Feet
    This series contains copies of studies contracted by the Rockefeller Brothers Fund regarding economic development prospects in Togo, Ghana, and Nigeria.
    - Togo - A Development Company for Togo: Economic Growth in a Small Market, 1963 March (Box 25, Folder 208)
      English and French versions.
    - Ghana, 1959-1961 (Box 25, Folder 209)
      Economic Feasibility of a Poultry Breeding Farm in Ghana, September 1959.
      Pakro Dam on the Kuia River: Project Report, February 1960.
      Economic and Technical Feasibility of a Machete Manufacturing Plant, December 1960.
    - Ghana - Feasibility Report on Plastics Industry in Ghana, 1961 February (Box 25, Folder 210)
    - Ghana - A Program to Accelerate Economic Growth in Ghana, 1961 July (Box 25, Folder 211)
    - Nigeria - Nigerian Housing Project, 1959 November (Box 25, Folder 212)
    - Nigeria, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 213)
      Economic Feasibility of a Meat Industry in Northern Nigeria, December 1959.
      Technological and Economic Feasibility of a Structural Clay Tile Plant for Western Nigeria, December 1959.
    - Nigeria, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 214)
      The Feasibility of Glass Production in Nigeria, Volume I: General Report, March 1960.
      The Feasibility of Glass Production in Nigeria, Volume II: Economic Reports, March 1960.
    - Nigeria, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 215)
      The Feasibility of Glass Production in Nigeria, Volume III: Technical Reports, March 1960.
      Nails Plant for Eastern Nigeria, May 1960.
      A Study of the Advisability of Building a Plant to Manufacture Electrical Appliances in Nigeria, August 1960.
    - Nigeria, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 216)
      Poultry and Egg Production for the Area Around Lagos, Nigeria, October 1960.
      Feasibility Report on Concrete Masonry Products Industry in the Federation of Nigeria, November 1960.
      The Economic and Technological Feasibility of a Machete Manufacturing Plant for Nigeria, November 1960.
    - Nigeria, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 217)
      Feasibility Report on Plastics Industry in the Federation of Nigeria, November 1960.
      The Potential for Lead Utilizing Industries in Nigeria, December 1960.
    - Nigeria - Prospectus for the Establishment of a Lead-Acid Automotive Storage Battery Company in Nigeria, 1960 December (Box 27, Folder 218)
    - Nigeria - Proposal for Glass Manufacturing Plants for Eastern Region Government of Nigeria, 1961 January (Box 27, Folder 219)
    - Nigeria - Techno-Economic Evaluation of Opportunities for Establishing a Textile Products Manufacturing Plant in Nigeria, 1961 February (Box 27, Folder 220)
    - Nigeria, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 221)
      Feasibility Report on Integrated Textile Mill in the Eastern Region of the Federation of Nigeria, March 1961.
      Report on Possibilities for Cigar Leaf and Cigar Production in Nigeria, June 1961.
    - Nigeria, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 222)
      Feasibility Report on Cement Manufacturing Industry in the Northern Region of the Federation of Nigeria, June 1961.
      Review of Feasibility: Nail Manufacturing Industry in the Eastern Region of the Federation of Nigeria, July 1961.
      A Feasibility Report on the Establishment of a Phonograph Record and General Plastics Industry in Nigeria, August 1961.
      Diversified Nigerian Wood Products Industries, 1961.
    - Nigeria, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 223)
      Feasibility Report on Metal Fastener Manufacture and Machine Shop in the Federation of Nigeria, April 1962.
      General Feasibility Survey of a Pharmaceutical Production Project for Nigeria, April 1962.